A Guide to the Harold P. Fabian papers FA071
Rockefeller Archive Center
Harold P. Fabian papers
1927-1981
Rockefeller Archive Center
Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated
Snake River Land Company
Fabian, Harold P.
FA071
26 Cubic Feet 70 document cases
Arrangement note
The Harold P. Fabian Papers are divided into eight series:
Series 1 - Snake River Land Company
Series 2 - Teton Companies
Series 3 - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc.
Series 4 - JY Ranch
Series 5 - Caneel Bay Plantations, Inc.
Series 6 - Conservation
Series 7 - Non-Textual Material
Series 1047 - Photographs
The arrangement of the collection does not reflect the file drawer index found in the first folder of the collection. The index can be used to identify topics but will not afford access. General topics, identified by Fabian, have been retained, but documents classified in the index in many subdivisions have been regrouped into larger units to provide more unified subjects. Land acquisition, leases, real estate activity, and a short run of files identified as JHP 1-29 have been kept in original order.
The arrangement of all the series is by type of material and within each type, to the extent possible, in chronological order.
Biographical/Historical note
Harold Pegram Fabian was born in Salt Lake City, Utah, on April 1, 1885. Mr. Fabian attended public schools in Salt Lake City and the Mercersburg (PA) Academy, received an A.B. from Yale in 1907 and an LL.B. from Harvard University in 1910. He returned to Salt Lake City and began practicing law in the firm of Dey, Hoppaugh and Fabian. He remained in Utah throughout his life and eventually became the senior partner in the firm of Fabian and Clendenin of Salt Lake City.
Through his partner, Beverly Clendenin, Fabian met Horace Albright, the Superintendent of Yellowstone National Park, around 1920 and formed a fast friendship. At the same time a group of Jackson Hole residents were making plans to preserve the Teton Mountains from unrestricted development and had recruited Albright to their cause. Albright, in turn, impressed John D. Rockefeller, Jr. with the vision of their plans while Mr. Rockefeller was on a tour of the West in 1926. Superintendent Albright took Mr. Rockefeller to view the Teton Mountains and Jackson's Hole, and Mr. Rockefeller very quickly began to organize a preservation plan. The firm of Fabian and Clendenin was contacted to act as counsel, and Fabian became the Western representative of Mr. Rockefeller and the person responsible for organizing and operating the Snake River Land Company. The Snake River Land Company was incorporated in 1927. It was formed to acquire property for eventual inclusion in the Grand Teton National Park. Fabian was not at first aware of the program's sponsor but probably knew by 1929, by which time the purchasing program was earnestly underway.
One of the immediate problems to arise was the continued operation of a tourist lodge and cabins at Moran, Wyoming. About 70,000 tourists per year went through Jackson Hole at the time, and tourism was an important facet of the local economy. The response was to organize the Teton Companies in 1930. Their purpose was to provide lodging and transportation for tourists in cooperation with the Yellowstone and Grand Teton National Parks.
This activity did not go unchallenged. Some local residents, especially cattle ranchers, resented what they considered to be a "takeover" by wealthy Easterners and a tyranny by the National Park Service. This disgruntlement led to several investigations. One of the most critical for the fledgling organization was conducted in 1930 by the Senate Special Committee on Wild Life Resources which examined the Land Company records, surveyed the country, and held hearings in Jackson Hole. The Committee returned a favorable report, finding no wrongdoing or scandalous machinations by Mr. Rockefeller, Jr. or the Snake River Land Company. Later investigations reported similar findings.
By 1933 the Snake River Land Company had acquired over 32,000 acres which fulfilled the majority of its purchasing program. With purchases mostly complete, the Company concentrated on management. It had acquired several ranches that were used to produce hay for the elk refuge, wildlife park and local market. It required a great deal of effort to refurbish, maintain and operate these ranches. There were encroachment problems and leases to negotiate and a good deal of intercourse between the Company and the Jackson Hole community to handle. Richard Winger filled a central role in fulfilling these functions. Overshadowing these daily affairs was a decade-long dispute with the Utah-Idaho Sugar Company over water rights in several lakes in the Jackson Hole area.
The Teton Companies were also very active throughout the 1930s. The Teton Investment Company was organized in 1930 and in turn organized the Teton Lodge Company and the Teton Transportation Company. The Lodge Company consisted of the Teton Lodge at Moran and the Jackson Lake Lodge on Jackson Lake. The Transportation Company provided the over-the-mountain connection between Jackson Hole, the Union Pacific Railroad, and Yellowstone National Park. In 1936 a reorganization merged the separate entities into the Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company, and in 1956 another reorganization let to the creation of the Grand Teton Lodge Company. The corporate changes reflected the growth of tourism and the need for facilities to accommodate that growth.
Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. was also formed to accommodate changing conditions. In 1940 the Land Company transferred its holdings to what shortly became the Jackson Hole National Monument. The new organization was formed to carry on the role of preservation. Property supervision continued, but increasingly more effort was directed toward enhancing the quality of the preserved area.
The restoration of Menor's Ferry was the first such effort. Fabian and his wife Josephine were deeply involved in this project to reconstruct the ferry and ranch buildings. Beyond the physical reconstruction they especially wanted to remember the pioneers of the area and their history. A wildlife park, constructed in 1946, was another effort to preserve the original beauty of Jackson Hole.
Concomitantly, Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. broadened its role by participating in conservation efforts throughout the United States. This was a result both of Laurance S. Rockefeller's energetic leadership and the general understanding that conservation is a national issue.
Harold Fabian retired from active business in 1954, but he never relinquished either his interest in Jackson Hole or his concern for conservation issues. He continued an active career working for conservation and historic preservation on both the national and state levels. He remained a Trustee of Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. until his death in 1975.
Scope and Contents note
The Harold P. Fabian Papers contain minutes, correspondence, financial records, reports, legal documents, photographs, audio tapes, motion picture film, and clippings which record Fabian's involvement in and operation of the Snake River Land Company, the Teton Companies, and Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. between 1927 and 1975. The papers are almost complete for the years 1927 to 1954. Correspondence comprises the bulk of the collection.
There were many facets to the Snake River Land Company and the related companies, and the Fabian Papers provide a very good record of the operation of a long-term philanthropic venture. The papers are especially revealing of the different levels of responsibility in an organization. On one level are the day-to-day affairs in which the practical and problem-solving aspects of carrying out policy are recorded. The decision-making and policy-making level is clearly defined, and the strategy and planning function is equally traceable through the correspondence. There is a substantial amount of personal correspondence throughout the collection which adds depth and background to the current events of the day.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IV 3A 07
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The Harold P. Fabian papers were donated to the Rockefeller Archive Center by Josephine Fabian in 1982. They were originally accessioned by the Rockefeller Family archives in 1963, as a collection relating to Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc., since Fabian was John D. Rockefeller Jr.'s representative in the development of Jackson Hole.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for scholarly research.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Environmental policy; Water rights; Philanthropy -- United States; Restoration and conservation; Philanthropy; Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated; Snake River Land Company; Fabian, Harold P.; Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated; Snake River Land Company; Fabian, Harold P.
- Snake River Land Company, 1927-1943; 1; 10 Cubic Feet 25 document cases
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains director's minutes, financial statements, correspondence, and reports relating to the Company established to implement the purchasing program for the future national park. Senate investigations, water rights, and land acquisition are the largest topics in this series.
  - File Drawer Index (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors - Minutes, 1927, 1931, 1937, 1940-1943 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Financial Journal, 1927-1929 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Financial Reports, 1929-1932, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bank Statements - Operating Account - Jackson State Bank, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Harold P. Fabian - Agent Account, 1931-1933, 1936-1941 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Snake River Land Company (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Bank Receipts - Continental National Bank, 1930-1934, 1942-1943 Statements, 1942-1943 Cancelled Checks, 1943
  - Bank Deposit Receipts - General Account - Jackson State Bank, 1939-1942 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Budget and Accounting - Correspondence, 1929-1933, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Budget and Accounting - Vouchers, 1928-1929, 1933, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Budget Summaries, 1940-1942 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Insurance Record - Snake River Land Company - Lodges and Ranches, ca. 1930-ca. 1947 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1927-May 1930 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1927-May 1930 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1927-May 1930 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, June 1930-1932 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, June 1930-1932 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, June 1930-1932 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, June 1930-1932 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1933-1940 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1933-1940 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1933-1940 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1933-1940 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1933-1940 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence - Horace M. Albright, 1927-1928, 1938-1939 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence - Kenneth Chorley, 1938-1940 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 28)
    Jack Eynon, 1920 John S. Turner, 1927-1928
  - Correspondence - Personal, 1929-1930, 1932-1933, 1935, 1937, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence - Property Taxes, 1928-1942 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence - Property Taxes, 1928-1942 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence - School District No. 3, Teton County, Wyoming, 1929-1930 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence - Vanderbilt Webb, 1939-1940, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence - Richard Winger, 1930-1933 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Schedules/Purchase Prices, S-1, 1929-1933 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Richard Winger Employment, S-1a, 1929-1943 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Mormon Row, S-2, 1929-1931, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Withdrawal Orders, S-4, 1927-1931 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Snake River Land Company (Box 6, Folder 39)
    Incorporation, S-100 Corporate Forms, S-103 Dissolution, S-103a
  - Fabian Clendenin, S-100 and S-100a, 1927-1941 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Corporate Affairs, S-102, 1927-1939, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Federal Income Tax Forms, S-104, 1931-1943 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Utah State Tax Forms, S-105, 1931-1943 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Elbo Ranch, 1929-1934, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Elbo Ranch - Inventories, 1930, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    Related Archival Materials note
    See also boxes 13 and 53.
  - Elbo Ranch - Budget and Accounting, 1930-1931, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Elbo Ranch - Receipts, 1930-1932, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Elbo Ranch - Receipts, 1930-1932, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Elbo Ranch - Receipts, 1930-1932, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Elk Ranch, 1939-1941 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Elk Ranch, 1939-1941 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Wyoming State Game Commission, 1929-1934, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Elk Commission, 1929-1934 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Wyoming Legislation, 1932-1943 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Plat Book of Jackson Hole Area - Purchasing Program, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Snake River Land Company (Box 8, Folder 56)
    Economic Survey of Jackson Hole Region, c. 1930 Regional Planning Commission, c. 1930
  - Map of Adjustments to Yellowstone National Park Boundaries, 1925 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    Found in 1928 Correspondence.
  - "Grand Teton National Park and Its Proposed Extension", November 7, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Map of Grand Teton National Forest with Parcels Marked, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Maps of 1930 and 1932 Plans for Park Extension (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Map of Engraving of Jackson Hole Area, November 11, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Map of Lands Withdrawn from Settlement Near Southern Yellowstone and Grand Teton National Parks, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - "The Proposal to Extend the Boundaries of Grand Teton National Parks", 1938 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - "A Plan for Grand Teton National Park", 1939 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Elk-Moran Road, 1929-1930 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Jackson Airport, 1940-1941, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - "The Grand Teton", 1931-1934 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - U. S. Senate Resolution 226 (72nd Congress), 1930-1934 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - U. S. Senate Resolution 226 (72nd Congress), 1930-1934 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - U. S. Senate Resolution 226 (72nd Congress) - Analysis of Opposition, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - U. S. Senate Resolution 226 (72nd Congress) - Procedures and General Statement of Snake River Land Company, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - U. S. Senate Resolution 226 (72nd Congress) - "Mr. John D. Rockefeller Jr.'s Proposed Gift of Land for the National Park System in Wyoming: A History of the Snake River Land Company and of the Efforts to Preserve the Jackson Hole Country for the Nation", 1933 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - U. S. Senate Resolution 226 (72nd Congress) - "Mr. John D. Rockefeller Jr.'s Proposed Gift of Land for the National Park System in Wyoming: A History of the Snake River Land Company and of the Efforts to Preserve the Jackson Hole Country for the Nation", 1933 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - U. S. Senate Resolution 226 (72nd Congress) - Hearings, August 7-10, 1933 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - U. S. Senate Resolution 226 (72nd Congress) - Robert D. Carey, 1931-1934 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - U. S. Senate Resolution 226 (72nd Congress) - Forest Service Policy, 1933-1934 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - U. S. Senate Resolution 3705 (73rd Congress), February 1934-May 1935 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - U. S. Senate Resolution 3705 (73rd Congress), February 1934-May 1935 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - U. S. Senate Bill 2972 (74th Congress), May 1935-1936 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - U. S. Senate Resolution 250 (75th Congress), 1938-1939 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    Hearings, August 8 and 10, 1938.
  - U. S. Senate Resolution 226 (72nd Congress) - Notes and Plans, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - U. S. Senate Resolution 226 (72nd Congress) - Transcript of Special Committee on Wildlife Resources, 1930-1933 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - "Acts of National Park Service in Discouraging People to Make Entries ...", 1926-1933 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Jackson's Hole "Courier", 1929-1933 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Jackson's Hole "Courier" - History of the Snake River Land Company - First Draft (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Jackson's Hole "Courier" - History of the Snake River Land Company - Preliminary Drafts (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Jackson's Hole "Courier" - History of the Snake River Land Company - Preliminary Drafts (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Jackson's Hole "Courier" - History of the Snake River Land Company - Preliminary Drafts (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Jackson's Hole "Courier" - History of the Snake River Land Company, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 89)
    Albright and Rayburn's Drafts, Hunter's Copy with Corrections.
  - Jackson's Hole "Courier" - History of the Snake River Land Company - First and Final Drafts, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - Jackson's Hole "Courier" - History of the Snake River Land Company - Index, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Jackson's Hole "Courier" - History of the Snake River Land Company - The "Courier" of April 13 and 27 and May 4, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - Chronology of Events, March 10, 1927-December 31, 1932 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Chronology of Events, December 4, 1933-May 6, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Chronology of Events, December 4, 1933-May 6, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Snake River Land Company (Box 13, Folder 96)
    Incorporation Papers, 1927 Dissolution Papers, 1940-1943
  - Corporate Reports to Secretary of State of Utah, 1928-1931 (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - Snake River Land Company (Box 13, Folder 98)
    Annual Statement to Secretary of State of Wyoming, 1928, 1931-1942 Certificate of Agent of Foreign Corporation, 1931
  - Elbo Ranch - Inventories, 1931-1932 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    See also boxes 7 and 53.
  - Buster Estes Petition for Right-of-Way, February 1931 (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - Jackson Airport - Western Airlines Petition, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 101)
  - Water Rights, 1923-1942 (Box 14, Folder 102)
  - Water Rights, 1923-1942 (Box 14, Folder 103)
  - Water Rights, 1923-1942 (Box 14, Folder 104)
  - Water Rights, 1923-1942 (Box 14, Folder 105)
  - Water Rights - Teton Irrigation Project Blueprints, 1913 (Box 14, Folder 106)
  - Water Rights (Box 14, Folder 107)
    Utah-Idaho Sugar Company Report, 1935 Snake River Land Company Protest, 1936
  - Water Rights - Deeds re: Snake River Land Company vs. Utah-Idaho Sugar Company, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 108)
  - Water Rights - Legal Briefs - Snake River Land Company vs. Utah-Idaho Sugar Company, June 1, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 109)
  - Water Rights - Transcript of Testimony - Snake River Land Company vs. Utah-Idaho Sugar Company, June 1, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 110)
  - Water Rights - Exhibits (Partial) - Snake River Land Company vs. Utah-Idaho Sugar Company, June 1, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 111)
  - Water Rights - Opinion and Order - Snake River Land Company vs. Utah-Idaho Sugar Company, December 3, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 112)
  - Water Rights - Appeal - State Board of Control - Snake River Land Company, April 24, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 113)
  - Water Rights - Appeal - Third Judicial District - Snake River Land Company vs. Utah-Idaho Sugar Company (Box 15, Folder 114)
  - Water Rights - Appeal - Wyoming Supreme Court - Snake River Land Company vs. Utah-Idaho Sugar Company, January 5, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 115)
  - Water Rights - Notes, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 116)
  - Water Rights - Map of Grand Teton National Park Extension Indicating Irrigation Canals, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 117)
  - Water Rights - Letter and Copies of Applications to be Sent to National Park Service, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 118)
  - Water Rights (Box 15, Folder 119)
    Agreement - Carlisle/Albert, 1935 Albert Applications, 1935
  - Water Rights - Water Diversion Plans, 1937-1938 (Box 15, Folder 120)
  - Water Rights - Water Diversion Plans - Legal Documents, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 121)
  - Water Rights - Water Power - Jackson Lake, 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 122)
  - Land Acquisition - Pending Entries, 1928-1933 (Box 16, Folder 123)
  - Land Acquisition - Pending Entries - Jessie P. Chambers, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 124)
  - Land Acquisition - Pending Entries - Robert L. Ferrin, 1929-1934 (Box 16, Folder 125)
  - Land Acquisition - Pending Entries - Eva Sanford Topping, 1930-1931 (Box 16, Folder 126)
  - Land Acquisition - Plans, ca. 1934 (Box 16, Folder 127)
  - Land Acquisition - Leases and Permits, 1936-1941 (Box 16, Folder 128)
  - Land Acquisition - Johnson (Coal Mine) - 3-45-113, 1930-1931 (Box 16, Folder 129)
  - Land Acquisition - Braman - 1-45-113, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 130)
  - Land Acquisition - Neil - 4-45-113, 1928, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 131)
  - Land Acquisition - Smith (Hatchet Ranch) - 7-45-113, 1930-1932 (Box 16, Folder 132)
  - Land Acquisition - Smith - 9-45-113, 1932, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 133)
  - Land Acquisition - Cowles - 14-45-113, 1932 (Box 16, Folder 134)
  - Land Acquisition - Feuz - 18-44-114, 1933, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 135)
  - Land Acquisition - Starrett (Mormon Row) - 8-42-225, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 136)
  - Land Acquisition - Taylor - 15-43-115, 1928-1930 (Box 16, Folder 137)
  - Land Acquisition - Steele (Mormon Row) - 17-43-115, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 138)
  - Land Acquisition - Almy - 18-43-115, 1930-1931 (Box 16, Folder 139)
  - Land Acquisition - Wardlaw - 21-43-115, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 140)
  - Land Acquisition - Harthoorn (Mormon Row) - 38-43-115, 1931, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 141)
  - Land Acquisition - Ferrel-Schwabacher - 55-43-115, 1928-1930, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 142)
  - Land Acquisition - Johnson - 1-46-115, 1930-1933 (Box 16, Folder 143)
  - Land Acquisition - Hammond (White Grass Ranch) - 12+13-43-116, 1929-1933, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 144)
  - Land Acquisition - Huyler (Pouch) - 15-43-116, 1929-1931 (Box 16, Folder 145)
  - Land Acquisition - Clark (Double Diamond Ranch) - 24-43-116, 1932-1933, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 146)
  - Land Acquisition - Karppi (Half Moon Ranch) - 24-43-116, 1929-1930, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 147)
  - Land Acquisition - Bark - Parcel 1 - 2-42-115, 1928-1930 (Box 17, Folder 148)
  - Land Acquisition - Kafferlin - Parcel 2 - 4-42-115 and 49-43-115, 1929-1933 (Box 17, Folder 149)
  - Land Acquisition - Erwin - Parcel 2a - 47-43-115 and 21-42-115, 1928-1930, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 150)
  - Land Acquisition - H. Bark (Miller) - Parcel 3 - 5-42-115, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 151)
  - Land Acquisition - Hoagland - Parcel 4 - 7-42-115, 1928, 1933-1934 (Box 17, Folder 152)
  - Land Acquisition - Elbo Ranch - Parcel 5 - 9-42-115, 1932 (Box 17, Folder 153)
  - Land Acquisition - Tyler - Parcel 6 - 12-42-115, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 154)
  - Land Acquisition - R. Brown - Parcel 7 - 13-42-115 and 18-42-116, 1928-1931, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 155)
  - Land Acquisition - Holten and Lovejoy - Parcel 8 - 14, 17 and 18-42-115, 1928-1930 (Box 17, Folder 156)
  - Land Acquisition - Edick - Parcel 9 - 15-42-115 and 19-42-116, 1928-1930, 1934 (Box 17, Folder 157)
  - Land Acquisition - Rinehart - Parcel 10 - 19-42-115, 1929-1932, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 158)
  - Land Acquisition - Call - Parcel 11 - 20-42-115, 1929-1930, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 159)
  - Land Acquisition - Crisp Estate - Parcel 12 - 35-42-115, 1930-1932 (Box 17, Folder 160)
  - Land Acquisition - May/Neilson - Parcel 13 - 36-42-115, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 161)